onestat.com 2015-12-26

# OneStat Web Analytics and Web Metrics - Privacy Center

To protect your privacy, OneStat.com has instituted policies that give you information and control.  
Our privacy statement covers: 

  1.  OneStat.com provides a link to this Privacy Statement on all pages that ask for personal information
  2.  OneStat.com will not release personal identifying information about you without first obtaining consent 
  3.  The information we collect
  4.  Our use of your information
  5.  How to change or deactivate your information 

When you visit an OneStat.com Client Web Site, we may collect general information that will not personally identify you, such as: 

  *  Internet browser
  *  Operating system
  *  Date of visit
  *  Time of visit
  *  Path taken through the site 

This information alone does not identify an individual and we will not combine it with information that does identify you as an individual. It provides statistics that we use to analyze and improve OneStat.com Client Web Sites. Through this "Aggregate Statistical Data," we are able to gain insights and a greater understanding of how people use our client Web sites. 

Personally identifiable information is defined as any personal information that could identify you, such as your name, address, telephone number, billing and shipping information, credit card information, or e-mail address.   
In general, when you visit an OneStat.com Client Web Site, you do not have to tell us who you are, or reveal any personally identifiable information. Because we take your privacy seriously, we will not collect any personally identifiable information unless you voluntarily provide it. At no time during your visit to an OneStat.com Client Web Site should you feel obligated to reveal any personal information to OneStat.com.   
We may share your personal information with third party suppliers and service providers, including independent contractors providing services for, or with OneStat.com. In all cases, these third parties are contractually required to keep that information confidential. They are not authorized by OneStat.com to use that information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for, or with OneStat.com. We may also disclose personally identifiable information to third parties if you consent to the disclosure, if we are compelled or authorized to do so by law, or if we reasonably believe there is a threat to someone's life or health. Personally identifiable information submitted for employment purposes will only be used in connection with the application process. It will not be used or disclosed for any other purposes unless required or authorized by law. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code). 

We may use customer contact information from the registration form to: 

  1.  send you information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners and
  2.  contact you when necessary

You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We may use "cookies" to gather statistical information that helps us understand what you find interesting and useful on our client Web sites. These cookies are known as your "Unique Visitor Cookie" and identify you only by random number (e.g. #12489). You can decline our cookies by adjusting the "accept cookies" setting on your browser, however this may affect the functionality of OneStat.com Client Web Sites.   
We may also embed a piece of code into pages of certain client Web sites. This gives us statistical site usage information about the pages visited, duration of page view, location previous to accessing the OneStat.com Client Web Site, the navigational habits of user, and browser and operating system. We do not use this code to collect any personally identifiable information 

This site contains links to other sites. OneStat.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web sites to which we link. We have special business relationships with some companies, but none of them receive individual identifying information about you collected at OneStat.com. 

We are committed to maintaining the security of the data we collect and protecting it from loss, misuse, or alteration. This applies to demographic information, client site usage information, and personally identifiable information. We store the data collected on secure OneStat.com servers that can be accessed only by authorized OneStat.com personnel.  
To safeguard all information collected, OneStat.com and all of its employees follow the practices in this policy. No one is permitted to access or use information for any purpose other than those explained in this policy. 

If you would like to change or deactivate the information you have submitted, please send a request using the contact form. OneStat.com will change or de-activate any information that could be used to identify you as soon as possible after your request, unless there we are required or authorized by law not to do so. Once de-activated your data will not be accessible, however due to limitations imposed by system backups to magnetic media, including the off site secure storage of data from our data warehouse your data can in some circumstances remain on these tapes. In the unlikely event that one of these tapes is accessed as part of a larger recovery of OneStat.com data, your data would continue to be flagged and remain de-activated and inaccessible for use by OneStat.com staff. 

To fully protect your privacy, we reserve the right to amend this policy at any time, and for any reason. We will post the amended terms on this Web site as they occur and encourage you to frequently check for updates. 

Nothing contained in this policy is intended to create a contract or agreement between OneStat.com and any user providing identifiable information in any form, whether visiting this site or any OneStat.com client site.   
We will take all necessary steps to comply with this privacy policy, however, to the extent permitted by law, nothing in this policy is intended to hold OneStat.com liable for any failure to comply with this policy.   
Further, because OneStat.com does not control the privacy practices of our clients, we advise that you read and fully understand their privacy policies. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us using the contact form.
